<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ACP Brasil</title>
    <link>https://www.acpbrasil.com/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ACP Brasil</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.acpbrasil.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://www.acpbrasil.com/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.acpbrasil.com/en/about/</guid>
      <description>What the video and know more about ACP in the words of the founder Greice Murphy    Advanced Care Partners (ACP) was founded in 2010 with the objective of changing the lives of nurses and families with sick entities, providing differentiated care in home nursing care to pediatric and adult patients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you interested?</title>
      <link>https://www.acpbrasil.com/en/form/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.acpbrasil.com/en/form/</guid>
      <description>  new RDStationForms(&#39;faca-parte-68cc8dd9cdaa1fe7fc07-html&#39;, &#39;UA-117751277-1&#39;).createForm();  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy ACP Brasil</title>
      <link>https://www.acpbrasil.com/en/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.acpbrasil.com/en/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Por favor, leia atentamente as seguintes declarações, pois elas abordam as regras de engajamento entre nós.
Queremos garantir que você respeite seus direitos de proteção de dados em conformidade com os mais recentes requisitos do Regulamento Geral de Proteção de Dados da UE (GDPR) a partir de 25 de maio de 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salaries and Benefits in ACP</title>
      <link>https://www.acpbrasil.com/en/salaries-and-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.acpbrasil.com/en/salaries-and-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Salaries and benefits will be entered between ACP and the nurse through contractual arrangements.
 Steve Francia   --  ACP Salaries  ACP offers career plans based on the experience of each professional; The salary is paid weekly to the nurse.    ACP Benefits Nurses will be received by the ACP team in the US and in addition to cost support they will have abode support and transportation for the first 30 days, as well as contact availability 24hs / 7 days a week throughout the contract time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you!</title>
      <link>https://www.acpbrasil.com/en/thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.acpbrasil.com/en/thanks/</guid>
      <description>Your form submission has been received Soon you will receive an email with the information you need to move forward in the process. Do not forget to check the SPAM.
See you soon!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>